peteranswers.com 2014-06-25

# Peter Answers - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

♦

### peteranswers.com Privacy Policy

♠

### Information we collect and how we use it:

In order to improve our Web site content, we may collect the following types of information:

♦ Cookies:

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on peteranswers.com.

♦ User options for cookie management:

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

♦ Information used by advertising companies:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

♦ Log information:

Like most standard Web site servers, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

♦ Information you enter in the petition and question textbox.
